# Jinhyeok Park

# Samsung Electronics (System LSI Business) RFIC Design Engineer

E-mail: ghyeak852@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/jinhyeok-park

## OBJECTIVE

To utilize my abilities and maximize my potential through a Ph.D. program and have a high-level engineering position in the future. Research interests include mm-wave integrated circuits (ICs) for the 5G, 6G communication systems, automotive radar sensors, and satellite communication systems.

## EDUCATION

03.2021 – 02.2023 M.S. in Electrical Engineering, KAIST, Korea

- Advisor: Prof. Songcheol Hong
- Dissertation: "Bidirectional VGA and Vector Modulator for 5G Communication Beamforming IC"
- Project 1: Multi-band true-time-delay phase shifter and bidirectional VGA for 5G wireless communication (Supported by Samsung Electronics)
- Project 2: Broadband beamforming IC for mm-wave 5G/B5G communication (Supported by Samsung Electronics)

03.2014 – 02.2021 B.S. in Electrical Engineering, Sungkyunkwan University, Korea

- Relevant coursework: Circuit Theory, Electronic Circuits, Physical Electronics, Semiconductor Electronics, Integrated Circuits
- ❖ GPA: 3.77/4

#### EXPERIENCE

03.2023 – present Engineer, Samsung Electronics (System LSI), RF Development Team, Korea

- Advisor : Hyun-chul Park
- ❖ 28/39GHz phased-array transceiver IC for the mobile device application
  - > Full path transceiver verifications and tests
  - ➤ Design RX feedback system (power detector, attenuator, and mixer)
- FMCW radar for the short-range detecting in mobile device
  - Design BIST (Built-In-Self-Test) system
     (SPDT switch, attenuator, RF/Baseband power detector, Loopback path)

07.2022 – 08.2022 Research Intern, Samsung Electronics (System LSI), RF Development Team, Korea

- Advisor: Hyun-chul Park
- \* EM simulations and characterizations for passive devices at mm-wave frequencies
- ❖ TEG Design for TRL calibration in GF22N FDSOI process

01.2020 – 02.2020 Student Researcher, **Seoul National University**, Mobile Multimedia Systems Group, Korea

- **❖** Advisor : Prof. Dongsuk Jeon
- Study of analog circuits (Wide bandwidth amplifier and folded cascode amplifier)

09.2019 – 12.2019 Student Researcher, Samsung Electronics (Memory), Solution Development Team, Korea

❖ Verification and analysis of analog circuits(PMIC, temperature sensor) used in SSDs

## PUBLICATIONS

## **Journal Publications**

1. <u>J. Park</u>, S. Hong. "Wideband Bidirectional Variable Gain Amplifier for 5G Communication," *IEEE Microwave and Wireless Technology Letters* (MWTL), 2023.

#### **Peer-Reviewed Conference Publications**

1. G. Lee, J. Lee, J. Park, S. Hong, "A 24-30GHz Wideband Power Amplifier with High-Coupling-Coefficient Transmission Line Transformer and Staggered Tuning." 2022 14th Global Symposium on Millimeter-Waves & Terahertz (GSMM), IEEE, 2022.

#### Presentations

1. <u>J. Park</u>, S. Hong. "Bidirectional Active Vector Modulator Using Impedance-Invariant Variable Gain Amplifier," Radio Science and Communications Conference. Korean Institute of Electromagnetic Engineering and Science (KIEES), 2022.

#### AWARDS & HONORS

#### **Awards**

Best Paper Award, Radio Science and Communication Conference, KIEES	11.2022
Best Paper Award Finalist, Global Symposium on Millimeter-Waves & Terahertz, IEEE	05.2022
Dean's List Award, Sungkyunkwan University, Korea	04.2019
Excellence Tutor Award, Sungkyunkwan University, Korea	12.2018

## **Scholarships**

03.2021 - 02.2023	EPSS (Educational Program for Samsung Semiconductor) Scholarship for MS students,
	Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd., Korea
03.2014 - 02.2021	Samsung Science Talent Scholarship, Samsung Co., Ltd., Korea

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

## Languages

Korean (Native)

English (Proficient)

## Computational & Design Tools

Advanced Design System (ADS), Cadence Virtuoso (Advanced)

- Design wideband bidirectional VGA, bidirectional phase shifter, power detector, mixer, switch, attenuator
- Used Samsung 28-nm bulk and FDSOI CMOS process, GF22N FDSOI process

## Python (Intermediate)

- Basic of deep learning and machine learning
- Pandas (Data analysis)

MATLAB, C (Novice)

#### Measurement Skills

Vector Network Analyzer, Vector Signal Generator, Signal Analyzer, mm-Wave component RF probing skills

## OTHER ACTIVITIES

Visiting Student, University of Colorado Boulder (Advisor : Prof. Zoya Popovic)

Circuit Theory Tutor, Sungkyunkwan University, Korea

Air Force Sergeant (TI&E), honorable discharge, Republic of Korea Air Force

12.2015 – 12.2017